Guide to the UE District 11 Records, 1940s-1990s UE.15.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- DeMaio-Rosen H, K, U #3 (Box 146)
- Allen –Bradley L. 1111 Milwaukee (Box 147)
- Coll. Pamphlets Pt. 2 and F. Rosen Labor Ed. Classes (Box 148)
- Oversize (Box 149)
- Dist Council – Bound minutes and addenda (Box 150)
- Frank Rosen and Newell, other Organizers (Box 151)
- UE Local 187, National Lead; District Council Minutes, 1969-1974 (Box 152)
- TLB Plastics (Box 153)
- TLB Plastics (Box 154)
- Stewart-Warner (Box 155)
- Terry Davis (Box 156)
- Sam Smucker (Box 157)
- Mulay Plastics (Box 158)
- Stewart-Warner Minutes, Grievances (Box 159)
- Stewart-Warner, Stewards Packets (Box 160)
- Organizing, Panallit, Local 1188 (GE) (Box 161)
- Stewart-Warner (Box 162)
- De Maio-Rosen Subj. Files L-Po (Box 163)
- Grand Exhaust & last minute (Box 164)
- De Maio-Rosen E-L (Box 165)
- UE D11 Local Files: Motec, 1146, 1128, 1138, 1111, 1132, 1154 (Box 166)
- Organizers Reports and Correspondence, 1940s (Box 167)
- Frank Rosen Notes and Research on the Economy (Box 168)
- Barco Mfg. (Box 169)
- Frank Rosen, 1970s-1980s (Box 170)
- Frank Rosen Early Union Work and early Dist 11 Org. Reports, 1940s (Box 171)
- Uppco, 172 (Box 172)
- Terry Davis IR, 1980s-1990s (Box 173)
- Companies, A-G and Photographs, esp. FE-CIO McCormick (Box 174)
- Acme Die Casting 1 of 3 (Box 175)
- Acme Die Casting 2 of 3 (Box 176)
- Acme Die Casting 3 of 3 (Box 177)
- Farm Equipment Workers (old) needs preservation attention (Harvester) (Box 178)
- Combustion Engineering and Misc. Locals 1154-1196 (Box 179)
- Organizers Reports – Bob Kingsley et al. (Box 180)
- Aetna Bearing, Local 151 (Box 181)
- Goodman Mfg Contracts (Box 182)
- Goodman, Part 2 (Box 183)